Finding aid for the Getty Education Institute for the Arts, Grant Files, 1984-2001 IA10021
Institutional Records and Archives
- Regional Institute grants, 1986-2001; II.; 61 Linear Feet (64 boxes)
  - Regional Grant Recipients
    - Minnesota Discipline-Based Art Education Consortium (University of Minnesota):
      - Implementation:
        - Year One:
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-23)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-23)
          - Grant Proposal, April 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-23)
          - Revised Grant Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-23)
          - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-23)
          - Final Report (Box 2007.IA.16-23)
        - Year Two:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-23)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Grant Offer Letter, May 9, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Collateral Materials/Summer Institute, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Student Assessment Proposal/Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Student Assessment Grant -- Contract (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Proposal: Minneapolis Institute of Arts (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
        - Year Three:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Grant Proposals (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Grant Offer Letter, June 13, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Interim Report (October 1991, Report Memo) (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Loose Report (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Fiscal Agent (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
        - Year Four:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - Monthly Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-24)
          - For Year 1992 Project Report & For Year 1993 Proposal/Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Site Visits (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - For Year 1993 Project Report & For Year 1994 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Year Five:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Assessment Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Loose Papers/Report (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Year Six:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Grant Offer Letter 9/14/94 (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - 501(c) (3) IRS Confirmation Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - For Year 1995 Proposal/For Year 1996 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
      - Strategic Planning Grant:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - SPG Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Grant Offer Letter 8/9/93 (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Vision Statement (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - [Loose folder, the Minnesota DBAE Consortium] (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
      - University of Minnesota [original grant award letters], 1989-1994 (Box 2009.IA.38-02)
    - North Texas Regional Institute for Educators on Visual Arts (North Texas State University):
      - Planning:
        - Grant offer letter, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
        - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
        - Correspondence with reviewers, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
        - Planning Grant report, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
        - Review grant proposal, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
        - Administrative memos, 1986-1987 (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
        - [Loose materials] (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
        - Budget, 1987-1989 (Box 2009.IA.38-01)
        - Grant proposal, 1986 (Box 2009.IA.38-01)
        - Dr. Jack Davis, 1989-1998 (Box 2009.IA.38-01)
      - Implementation:
        - Year One:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
          - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-36)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Development Plan (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Supplemental Student Evaluation Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
        - Year Two:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Miscellaneous/1991 Summer Institutional Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - 1991 Project Report & 1992, Proposal October 25, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Student Assessment proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
        - Year Three:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Grant Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - [Loose North Texas Institute Report, June 15-26, 1992] (Box 2007.IA.16-37)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Student Assessment (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - Year Four:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - For Year 1993 Project Report and For Year 1994 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Collateral Material (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - National Specialty, Fiscal Year 1995:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Grant Offer Letter, October 13, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Progress Report 9/94 to 11/94 (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Progress Report 12/94 to 3/95 (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
          - Progress Report 4/95 to 8/95 (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1995:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Progress Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - For Year 1994 Project Report and For Year 1995 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
        - National Specialty Program, Fiscal Year 1996:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - April Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - October Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - December Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1996:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - October Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - December Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - April Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
        - National Specialty Program, Fiscal Year 1997:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-39)
          - November 1996 Mini-conference (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - December 1996/April 1997 Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - October 1996 Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1997:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Original & Revised for 1997 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Advocacy Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1998:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
        - National Specialty Program, Fiscal Year 1998:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Progress Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1999:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 2000 (Year 10):
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Collateral materials (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Grant offer letter (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 2001 (Year 11):
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Collateral materials (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Grant offer letters (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
          - Internal memos (Box 2007.IA.16-40)
      - Strategic Planning Grant:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - Grant Offer Letter, August 9, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - SPG Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - Implementation Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - Vision Statement (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
        - Technical Assistance Visit (Box 2007.IA.16-38)
    - Ohio Partnership for the Visual Arts: Regional Institute for Educators (Ohio State University):
      - Planning:
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
        - Grant Proposal, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
        - Planning Grant Report (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
        - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
        - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
        - Grant Offer Letter, May 20, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
        - Grant proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
      - Implementation:
        - Year One:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Grant Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Grant Offer Letter April 6, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Interim Report 1 (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Site Visit, Summer 1988/Summer Institute (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Interim Report 2 (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Final Financial Report, May 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
        - Year Two:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - 1989 Summer Institute Notebook (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - [Loose For Year 1990 Project Report] (Box 2007.IA.16-41)
          - For Year 1991 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Student Assessment Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
        - Year Three:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Interim Report Memos (1 & 2) (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - [Loose: Year 3 Project report], March 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Student Assessment Grant: Contract (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Assessment Grant (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
        - Year Four:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Interim Report Memos 1 & 2 (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Collateral Materials/Summer Institute 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Student Assessment Grant (Proposal) (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
        - Year Five:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - Collateral Materials/Summer Institute Materials 1992 (Box 2007.IA.16-42)
          - For Year 1992 Project Report/For Year 1993 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - [Loose: The Ohio Partnership for the Visual Arts: Regional Institute for Educators, Report] (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Student Assessment Grant (for year 1993) (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Student Assessment Phase II Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
        - Year Six:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - [Loose papers and reports: The Ohio Partnership for the Visual Arts: Regional Institute for Educators] (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Collateral Materials/Summ. Institute Material (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - For Year 1993 Project Report/For Year 1994 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Student Assessment Grant (for year 1994) (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
        - Year Seven:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - For Year 1994 Project Report/For Year 1995 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-43)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Student Assessment Grant (for year 1995) (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - National Specialty Program, Fiscal Year 1995:
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Progress Report 12/94 to 3/95 (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Progress Report 9/94 to 11/94 (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Summer Program Information 1995 (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - National Specialty Program, Fiscal Year 1996:
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - October Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Loose Papers/Reports (includes videocassette, photos, and slides) (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Summer 1996 Leadership Academy (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1996:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - December Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
          - October Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - April Progress Report (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - [Loose Final Narrative, Student Assessment Project, December 1996 (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1997:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Original & Revised FY1997 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Report for the OPVA Phase II Student Assessment Grant (loose) (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Student Assessment (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Fiscal Year 1997:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Grant Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Progress Report, 12/96 to 4/97 (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Progress Report, December 1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - April-August Report (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Student Assessment Grant – Fiscal Year 1997 (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Core Program, Fiscal Year 1998:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Fiscal Year 1999:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-45)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 2000, (Year 12):
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Budget (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Correspondence (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Internal Memos (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 2001, (Year 13):
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Budget (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Correspondence (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Internal Memos (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2010.IA.21-01)
      - Strategic Planning Grants:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - Grant Offer Letter 8/9/93 (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - SPG Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - Vision Statement (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - Technical Assistance Visit (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
        - Implementation Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-44)
      - Ohio State University [original grant award letters], 1988-1998; (3 folders) (Box 2009.IA.38-01)
    - Prairie Visions: The Nebraska Consortium (Nebraska Department of Education):
      - Planning:
        - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Grant Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Grant Offer Letter, May 4, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Planning Grant Report (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
        - Final Report (Box 2007.IA.16-25)
      - Implementation:
        - Year One:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Correspondence File 1 (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Correspondence File 2 (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Grant Proposal, June 2, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Review (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Press (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Final Report (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Collateral Material (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - NAEA Presentation, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Prairie Visions Summer Institute, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
        - 1988 Leadership Program:
          - Final Narrative & Budget Report (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Grant Offer Letter, April, May, June 1988 (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
          - Site Visit, Summer 1998 (Box 2007.IA.16-26)
        - Year Two:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - Grant Offer Letter (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - ASCD Conference, March 1991, San Francisco (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - Report, July 1990 (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - Report, March 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - Prairie Visions Summer Institute 1990 Material (Box 2007.IA.16-27)
          - Report and Summer Institute Material July 1, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
        - Year Three:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
          - Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
          - Grant Offer Letter 6/13/91 (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
          - Interim Report (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
          - [Loose: reports and bundled papers regarding Nebraska Department of Education (Prairie Visions)] (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
        - Year Four:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-28)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-29)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-29)
          - Grant Offer Letter 7/8/92 (Box 2007.IA.16-29)
          - Interim Reports (Box 2007.IA.16-29)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-29)
          - 1992 Project Report & 1993 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-29)
          - July 1992 Report (Box 2007.IA.16-29)
          - [Loose reports and bundled papers regarding Nebraska Department of Education (Prairie Visions)] (Box 2007.IA.16-29)
          - Loose Reports in six folders: 1991-92 (Box 2007.IA.16-30)
        - Year Five:
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-30)
          - Correspondence (Box 2007.IA.16-30)
          - Budget (Box 2007.IA.16-30)
          - Grant Offer Letter, 9/14/93 (Box 2007.IA.16-30)
          - Collateral Materials (Box 2007.IA.16-30)
          - 1994 Project Report / 1995 Proposal (Box 2007.IA.16-30)
          - [Loose: Papers and Reports regarding Nebraska Department of Education] (Box 2007.IA.16-30)
          - [Loose: Papers and Reports regarding Nebraska Department of Education: Prairie Visions 1992-1994] (Box 2007.IA.16-31)
        - Core, Fiscal Year 1995 (Year 6):
          - Internal Memos (Box 2007.IA.16-32)